Moore, Frank C.; Papers apap223
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Speeches, 1934-1969; 10; 10 cubic ft.
  - Speeches, 10.79 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 1)
    - b. Plattsburgh, N.Y. Dedication of Harrington Hal dormitory. Plattsburgh State Teachers, 05/05/1959
    - c. New York, N.Y. 50th Annual Meeting of Conference of Mayors, Waldorf - Astoria Hotel, 05/09/1959
  - Speeches, 10.80 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 2)
    - a. Geo. Hallett Dinner, Citizens Union, Columbia University Club. NYC, 10/20/1959
    - b. State University of New York - Dedication of Dormitories. College of Education, Oswego, N.Y., 11/09/1959
    - c. New York Library Association - 66th Annual Conference, Hotel Commodore - NYC, 11/12/1959
    - d. National Municipal League 65th Annual National Conference on Government. Springfield, Massachusetts, 11/17/1959
    - Municipal Section, NYS Bar Assn., Annual Meeting, Hotel Commodore, New York City, 01/28/1960 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 3)
  - Speeches, 10.81 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 4)
    - a. Town Association Annual Meeting, Hotel Commodore, NYC, 02/08/1960
    - b. County Officers Assn. Mid - Winter Conference - Hotel Syracuse, Syracuse, New York, 03/22/1960
    - c. SUNY Downstate Med Center 110th Anniversary Convocation. Brooklyn, New York, 03/30/1960
    - d. Hudson Valley Technical Institute Groundbreaking Ceremonies for Campus. Troy, New York, 04/20/1960
  - Speeches, 10.82 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 5)
    - a. Dinner, Annual Participating Fund for Legal Education, University of Buffalo. Buffalo, NY, 05/02/1960
    - b. Board of Overseers, Albert Einstein College of Medicine "Need for University Hospital", 05/24/1960
    - c. Opening Session of Conference on Local Government, Brubacher Hall, College of Education, Albany, N.Y., 06/06/1960
    - d. Albert Einstein College of Medicine - Board of Overseers Meeting, NYC, 06/09/1960
  - Speeches, 10.83 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 6)
    - a. 51st Annual Meeting N.Y.S. Conference of Mayors & Other Munc. Officials, Manager Hotel, Rochester, N.Y., 06/20/1960
    - b. Fall Conference of County Officers - Governor Rockefeller's Speech - Delivered by FCM, 09/12/1960
    - c. Harpur College Dedication of Buildings, Binghamton, NY, 09/26/1960
    - d. Testimonial Diner for John Cooke. St John's School Hall, Alden, N.Y., 10/01/1960
    - e. Faculties Assn. of College of Education Bi - Ennial Meeting. Sheraton - Ten Eyck - Albany, N.Y., 10/13/1960
    - Joint Legis. Committee for School Financial Education Building, Albany, N.Y., 10/15/1960 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 7)
  - Speeches, 10.84 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 8)
    - a. Seminar on "State Government & the Metropolitan Area" University of N.C. - Chapel Hill - North Carolina, 12/03/1960
    - b. Michigan State Assn. of Supervisors, Jack Tar Hotel, Lansing, Mich. Delivered by B. Marshlow, 01/24/1961
    - c. N.Y.S. Bar Assn. - Hotel Roosevelt, 01/26/1961
  - Speeches, 10.85 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 9)
    - a. Memorial Services for Assn. of Fire District Officers - Hotel Buffalo, Buffalo, N.Y., 02/06/1961
    - b. County Officers Assn. Executive Bd. Meeting, Parrott House - Schoharie, N.Y., 03/03/1961
    - c. Dedication of Feinberg Library, College of Education, Plattsburgh, 03/04/1961
    - d. Remarks by Frank C. Moore. Erie County Tech. Institute, 03/12/1961
    - e. Remarks by Frank C. Moore. Fire Safety Con. Nelson House - Pksy, 09/13/1961
    - f. Founder's Day Convocation, SUNY College at Oswego, 10/18/1961
    - g. Nassau County Village Officials Assn - Lynbrook, N.Y., 11/14/1961
  - Speeches, 10.86 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 10)
    - a. Annual Conference National Municipal League. Miami, Florida, 1961 November 30-1961 December 01
    - b. Governmental Research Bureau, Hotel Statler, Buffalo, N.Y., 12/11/1961
  - Speeches, 10.87 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 11)
    - a. Dinner Meeting of Erie County Mayors Conference. East Aurora, N.Y., 01/18/1962
    - b. Municipal Section, N.Y.S. Bar Assn., Commodore Hotel. New York City, 01/25/1962
    - Opening Session Assn., Towns Annual Meeting, Statler - Hilton Hotel, Buffalo, 1962 February 14 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 1)
    - Municipal Corporation, 1962 March 02 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 2)
    - Class in "Local Government in N.Y.S.", Graduate Program in Public Administration, Albany, New York, 1962 March 05 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 3)
    - Conference, Rotary Clubs Dist. 709, Hotel Statler, Buffalo, 1962 May 04 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 4)
    - Dutchess County Assessors Assn., Anchor Inn, Poughkeepsie, NY, 1962 May 15 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 5)
    - Testimonial for John Nichols, County Gentlemen Res., Saratoga Springs, New York, 1962 May 16 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 6)
    - Dedication of Buildings and luncheon, SUNY College at Geneseo, 1962 May 17 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 7)
    - Dedication of Buildings and luncheon, SUNY College at Cortland, 1962 May 23 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 8)
    - Open House and Dedication, Cortlandville, NY Town Hall, 1962 May 22 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 9)
    - National County Officers Conference, Hotel Statler, NYC, 1962 July 10 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 10)
    - County Officers Fall Conference, Hotel Concord, Kiamesha Lake, 1962 September 10 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 11)
    - NYS Association of School District Administrators Grossingers, 1962 October 10 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 12)
    - Library Trustees Foundation of NYS, Albany Presentation by FCM, 1962 October 17 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 13)
    - Dedication Ceremonies, Jamestown Community College, Jamestown, New York, 1962 November 11 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 14)
    - Village Officials Assn., Lynbrook, New York, 1962 November 14 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 15)
    - Conference on Assessors' Administration, Hotel Roosevelt, NYS Assessors Assn, 1963 January 14 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 16)
    - "Improving Local Assessments", Assn. of Towns, Hotel Commodore, NYC, 1963 February 04 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 17)
    - Remarks by Frank C. Moore, at Assn. of Towns, NYC, 1963 February 05 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 18)
    - Municipal Section of Bar Assn., Panel on Home Rule, 1963 January 24 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 19)
    - Opening Session, Assn. of Towns, Hotel Commodore, NYC, 1963 February 04 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 20)
    - Groundbreaking at Downstate Medical Center, 1963 February 14 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 21)
    - "Testimonial Dinner for John Burns", Garden City Hotel, 1963 March 14 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 22)
    - FCM's Talk with Gov. and Legislative Leaders re Home Rule, 1963 March 29 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 23)
    - Dedication Luncheon, State University College at Buffalo, 1963 April 24 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 24)
    - (Buffalo) Erie County Tax Committee, 1963 May 14 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 25)
    - University of Buffalo, FCM remarks Receiving Capen Award, 1963 June 01 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 26)
    - Municipal Law Seminar Speech, Ten Eyck, Albany, 1963 June 05 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 27)
    - State University College at Potsdam, 1963 June 09 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 28)
    - Graduate School of Public Affairs, 1963 June 18 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 29)
    - County Officers Assn. Speech, Hotel Concord, Sept 11, 1963 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 30)
    - Article in October 1963 Issue Local Government Law Service Letter (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 31)
    - St. Lawrence University, Canton, NY, Inauguration Of Pres. & Degree to FCM, 1963 October 19 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 32)
    - NYS School Board Assn. Convention, Syracuse, NY, FCM keynoter and panelist, 1963 October 29 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 33)
    - County Officers Assn. 40 Annual conference, Buffalo, 1964 January 28 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 34)
    - Home Rule Panel at Assn. of Town Meeting, FCM moderated, 1964 February 10 (Box 51 (10-Speeches), Folder 35)
  - Speeches, 10.88 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 1)
    - a. Third Annual Municipal Law Seminar. Albany, NY, 1964 June 05
    - b. Monroe Community College 1st Commencement. Rochester, NY, 1964 June 12
    - New York State Conference of Mayors and Other Municipal Officials. Albany, NY, 1964 June 16 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 2)
  - Speeches, 10.89 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 3)
    - a. Lieutenant Governors' Conference. New York, NY, 1964 August 21
    - b. Annual Conference of Trustees of Councils of Two - Year Colleges. Lake Placid, NY, 1964 October 03
  - Speeches, 10.90 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 4)
    - a. Dedication of Buffalo & Erie County Public Library. Buffalo, NY, 1964 October 16
    - b. Local Government Seminar, Health Dept. Albany, NY, 1964 October 14
    - c. Onondaga Student Legislature. Syracuse, NY, 1964 October 15
  - Speeches, 10.91 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 5)
    - a. Testimonial Dinner for Ed Jaeckle. Buffalo, NY, 1964 October 27
    - b. Open House and Reception, Manhattan Community College. New York, NY, 1964 December 03
    - Association of Towns, Annual Meeting. New York, NY, 1965 February 08 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 6)
  - Speeches, 10.92 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 7)
    - a. Capen Award and Commencement, SUNY at Buffalo. Buffalo, NY, 1965 February 12
    - b. State Legislative Conference of the Business & Professional Women's Clubs of New York State. Albany, NY, 1965 February 22
    - Introduction of Governor Rockefeller at Gould Inauguration, 1965 May 13 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 8)
    - Associated Industries of New York State. Lake Placid, New York, 1965 September 24 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 9)
    - Associated Industries of New York State. Lake Placid, New York, 1965 September 24 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 10)
  - Speeches, 10.93 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 11)
    - a. Association of Towns, Annual Meeting. New York, NY, 1965 February 08
    - b. Introduction of President, State University of New York, Samuel B. Gould. Binghamton, NY, 1965 September 30
    - Office for Local Government Workshop. Binghamton, NY, 1965 September 30 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 12)
    - President's Dinner. Buffalo, NY, 1965 December 14 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 13)
    - Orientation Program for Legislators. Albany, NY, 1966 January 06 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 14)
    - General Electric Officials Luncheon. Ten Eyck, Albany, NY, 1966 February 01 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 15)
    - Association of Towns, Annual Meeting. New York, NY, 1966 February 08 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 16)
    - OLG Committee on Reapportionment. New York, New York, 1966 February 24 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 17)
    - Mayor's Conference, 1966 April 12 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 18)
    - County Officers Association, Meeting on Reapportionment. Albany, NY, 1966 May 19 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 19)
    - Television Program, W - TEN. Albany, NY, 1966 July 14 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 20)
    - Rotary Club of Albany, Inc. Albany, NY, 1966 July 14 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 21)
    - Office for Local Government, Regional Meeting. Rome, NY, 1966 July 22 (Box 52 (10-Speeches), Folder 22)
  - Speeches, 10.94 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 1)
    - a. Allied Printing Trades Council Dinner. Utica, NY, 1966 August 03
    - b. Office for Local Government, Regional Meeting. Plattsburgh, NY, 1966 August 30
    - Republican State Convention, Nomination of Attorney General Louis J. Lefkowitz. Rochester, NY, 1966 September 08 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 2)
    - Office for Local Government, Meeting of County Officers Association. Kiamesha Lake, 1966 September 12 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 3)
  - Speeches, 10.95 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 4)
    - a. Associated Industries of New York State. Whiteface Inn, Lake Placid, NY, 1966 September 16
    - b. School Boards Association, "Your School Board in Action" radio series aired in mid-September, Undated
    - Hamilton County Republican Committee, biennial dinner. Indian Lake, NY, 1966 October 13 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting of the Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York at Ithaca College. Ithaca, NY, 1966 October 18 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 6)
    - NY State School Boards Association, Annual Convention. Syracuse, NY, 1966 October 24 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 7)
    - Empire State Chamber of Commerce. New York, NY, 1966 October 25 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 8)
  - Speeches, 10.96 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 9)
    - a. Workshop of the District Legislative Chairmen of the New York State Congress of Parents and Teachers. Albany, NY, 1966 November 16
    - b. State Board of Equalization & Assessment Budget Hearing. Albany, NY, 1966 November 19
    - Municipal Law Section, New York State Bar Association. New York, NY, 1967 January 27 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 10)
    - OLG Annual Meeting of the Association of Towns. New York, NY, 1967 February 06 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 11)
  - Speeches, 10.97 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 12)
    - a. New School for Social Research. New York, NY, 1967 February 23
    - b. Annual Legislators' Seminar of New York State Council of Churches. Albany, NY, 1967 February 27
    - State University of New York, University Television Network, Channel 17 appearance. New York, NY, 1967 March 30 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 13)
  - Speeches, 10.98 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 14)
    - a. The Fifty Group. Latham, NY, 1967 May 01
    - b. Committee on Local Government and Home Rule. Albany, NY, 1967 May 09
    - Committee on Intergovernmental Relations. Albany, NY, 1967 May 16 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 15)
  - Speeches, 10.99 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 16)
    - a. Commencement of Adirondack Community College. Hudson Falls, New York, 1967 June 06
    - b. Nichols School, address to students. Buffalo, NY, 1967 November 10
  - Speeches, 10.100 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 17)
    - a. Advisory Board of the Office for Local Government at the Annual Meeting of the Association of Towns. New York, NY, 1968 February 06
    - b. State University College, Fredonia. Fredonia, NY, 1968 May 13
    - Albany Law School Commencement. Albany, NY, 1968 June 05 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 18)
    - Annual Fall Conference of the County Officers Association. Kiamesha Lake, NY, 1968 October 08 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 19)
    - Annual Banquet of the Association of Towns. New York, NY, 1969 February 11 (Box 53 (10-Speeches), Folder 20)